cgsociety.org 2011-11-23

# 

## CGSociety Privacy Policy

### Introduction

We are committed to respecting your privacy. 

This document constitutes the Privacy Policy under which you may use CGSociety. Your use of CGSociety constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use CGSociety or any associated services. By using CGSociety, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

We are dedicated to providing a safe and secure user experience. This Privacy Policy tells you how we use personal information collected by us. You are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy whenever you visit CGSociety to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

This Privacy Policy is for CGSociety only. If you link to other websites, we encourage you to review their privacy policies so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other web sites to which you choose to link to from CGSociety. This Privacy Policy applies solely to the information we collect via CGSociety and does not apply to information we collect in any other fashion. 

Your data will be stored and processed in whole or in part in the United States. If you access CGSociety outside the United States, your usage constitutes consent to the transfer of your data out of your country and to the United States. You also agree that your data may be transferred to any other country. 

We usually collect personal information directly from you although sometimes we may use agents or service providers to do this for us. We may also acquire lists from other sources, both from other companies and from other public documents. 

### Collection and Use of Information

We may request that you provide personal information, including your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number credit card number, social security number, contact information, billing information and any other information from which your identity is discernible. We may collect demographic information that is not unique to you such as your ZIP code, age, preferences, gender, interests and favourites. Sometimes we may collect a combination of the two types of information. 

We may also gather certain information about your use of CGSociety's services, such as what areas you visit and what services you access. Moreover, there is information about your computer hardware and software that may be collected by us. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring web site addresses.We may ask to provide descriptive, cultural, behavioural, preferential and/or life style information about yourself, but it is solely up to you whether you furnish such information. 

### Public Information

Any information posted on bulletin boards and/or communicated in chat areas becomes public information. While we strive to protect and respect your privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose in public areas. 

###  CGJobs Resumes and Profiles

We give you a number of options regarding the accessibility of your resume: 

  1. You can store your resume in our database, but not allow it to be searchable by potential employers. Not allowing your resume to be searchable means that you can use it to apply for a job online, but employers and recruiters will not have access to search it through our resume database product. 
  2. If you allow your resume to be searchable without making it confidential and hiding your contact information, then all parties with access to our searchable resume database will have access to your resume.
  3. If you have a confidential resume, but apply to a job posting on CGJobs, the employer to whom you send your resume will be able to view your contact information.

In addition, portions of your searchable resume may be made public in your CGJobs profile. 

We attempt to limit access to our resume database only to employers, recruiters, hiring managers, and human resource professionals, as well as law enforcement and national security agencies, but cannot guarantee that other parties will not gain access to this database. We are not responsible for the use made of resumes by third parties who access such resumes while they are in our searchable database. However, the portions of your searchable resume that are automatically made public in your CGJobs profile are accessible to anyone who uses the CGJobs service. 

You may remove your resume on CGJobs or delete your profile on CGJobs at anytime, but, employers, recruiters and others who have paid for access to the CGJobs resume database or to obtain a copy of that database or have paid for access to the CGJobs services, as well as parties who have otherwise gained access may have retained a copy of your resume or CGJobs profile in their own files or databases. We are not responsible for the retention, use or privacy of resumes or profiles in these instances. 

If you apply for a position on CGJobs, you may be asked to provide information on your gender, race or other protected status where permitted by applicable law. Some employers are required by law to gather this information from job applicants for reporting and record-keeping requirements. 

### Use of Your Information

We use the information we gather on CGSociety, whether personal, demographic, collective or technical, for the purpose of operating and improving CGSociety's services, fostering a positive user experience, and delivering the products that we offer. If you have provided consent for us to do so, we may also use the information we gather to inform you of other products or services available from us or our affiliated companies. 

We may use your contact information in order to send you e-mail or other communications regarding CGSociety's products and services, to contact you about your opinion of current products and services or potential new products and services that may be offered. The nature and frequency of these messages will vary depending upon the information we have about you. 

In addition, you may receive free newsletters from us relating to topics that may be of special interest to you. All such newsletters have the facility for you to easily unsubscribe from the particular mailing list. We have areas on CGSociety where you can submit feedback. Any feedback you submit in these areas becomes our property, and we can use such feedback for marketing purposes or to contact you for further information. 

We also share aggregated information about visitors to CGSociety with our clients, partners and other third parties so that they can understand the kinds of visitors to CGSociety and how those visitors use CGSociety. 

### Third Party and Co-Branded Sites

We may establish relationships with business partners that allow visitors to CGSociety to link directly to sites operated by these partners. Some of these sites may be co-branded with our logo; however, these sites may not be operated or maintained by or on our behalf. These sites may collect personal information from you that may be shared with us. This Privacy Policy will apply to any personal information we obtain in this manner. 

We are not responsible for the content or practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our sites. These links are meant for your convenience only. Links to third party sites do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement or approval by us of the content, policies or practices of those third party sites. Once you have left CGSocietys via such a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site. 

### Information Disclosure

Disclosure to third parties of your personal information, combined personal and demographic information or information about your use of CGSociety's services may occur as described below. We may disclose information to third parties if you consent to such disclosure. For example, if you indicate that you would like to receive information about the products or services of third parties, we may supply your contact information to third parties such as employers, recruiters, data aggregators, marketers or others for the purpose of sending you e-mail or otherwise communicating with you. We may use data we have about you to determine whether you might be interested in the products or services of a particular third-party. 

We may disclose information to companies and individuals we employ to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include hosting our web servers, analysing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These companies and individuals will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but they may not share that information with any other third party. 

We may disclose information if legally required to do so, if requested to do so by a governmental entity or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; protect our rights or property or that of our affiliated companies; prevent a crime or protect national security; or protect the personal safety of users or the public. 

We may disclose and transfer information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of our business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event we may become the subject of a bankruptcy proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, we or our trustee in bankruptcy may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court. 

We may also share aggregated anonymous information about our visitors with our clients, partners and other third parties so that they may understand the kinds of visitors to CGSociety and how those visitors use CGSociety. 

### Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place commercially reasonable and suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors have access to this information. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. 

Your credit card information is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer protocol. SSL makes it difficult for your credit card information to be intercepted or stolen while being transmitted. We use a service company to process credit card transactions and we do not store your credit card details. 

We will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access of your personal information. 

You can also play an important role in keeping your personal information secure, by maintaining the confidentiality of any CGSociety passwords and accounts. Please notify us immediately if there is any unauthorised use of your account by any other user or any other breach of security. 

### Cookies, Applets and Web Beacons 

We may use cookies, applets, web beacons and other devices (collectively known as tracking technology). Personal information cannot be collected via tracking technology. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. If do not wish to receive cookies you can instruct your web browser to refuse them. However, doing so will prevent access to some areas of CGSociety and limit your use of some services. 

### Access to and Modification of Your Information

You may review, correct, update or change your information at any time. You may also opt out of receiving newsletters and certain other information from us. To change your information, simply log into your account and edit it with the options provided. 

We retain indefinitely all the information we gather about you in an effort to make your repeat use of CGSociety more efficient, practical, and relevant. You can close and delete your information from our online database in which event we will remove all our copies of your information except for an archival copy which is not accessible on the Internet. 

You have a right to access most personal information we hold about you and if we deny access in some circumstances we will tell you why. To request access, please contact our privacy officer as set out at Contact Information. 

### Privacy Policy Changes

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted to this page. 

### Contact Information

Please contact our Privacy Officer to ask for access to your information or if you have a complaint concerning your information privacy or if you would like more information about our approach to privacy.
